<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>security on 10degres</title>
    <link>https://10degres.net/tags/security/</link>
    <description>Recent content in security on 10degres</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://10degres.net/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GitHub search</title>
      <link>https://10degres.net/github-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://10degres.net/github-search/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We all know the famous quote &amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;Think out of the box&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo;.
Technical knowledge is important but creativity is also.
In bug bounty, to get nice rewards, sometimes you don&amp;rsquo;t need to be a crazy coder or great network engineer, you simply need to try what other didn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year, Slack get in trouble because many developers leave their credentials in their public repository.
Last year Uber had to deal with a major security issue: database keys were stored in GitHub (this leads to a sweet bounty for the finder).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found an interesting project, on GitHub itself, to parse the search engine results: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/melvinsh/vcsmap&#34;&gt;vcsmap from Melvinsh&lt;/a&gt;.
Unfortunately the scrapper seems to have trouble with search that required authentication.
Since I don&amp;rsquo;t understand Ruby, I wrote my own tool with PHP.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure your Wordpress</title>
      <link>https://10degres.net/secure-your-wordpress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://10degres.net/secure-your-wordpress/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With more than 60 million websites, WordPress is the most popular CMS currently in use but it&amp;rsquo;s also based on the most hacked environment aka LAMP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As we all know, there is no way to stop a determined hacker but you can slow him down or detect him before things become serious.
Below some techniques to improve the security of your site. 
This post is directly inspired from &lt;a href=&#34;http://codex.wordpress.org/Hardening_WordPress&#34;&gt;Wordpress official codex&lt;/a&gt; and some hackers techniques I learned last months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;files&#34;&gt;Files&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Worpdress documentation, and I won&amp;rsquo;t discuss this point here, directories must have the following permission: &lt;code&gt;drwxr-xr-x&lt;/code&gt; (755) and files must be: &lt;code&gt;-rw-r--r--&lt;/code&gt; (644).
Wordpress says that automatic update changes file/dir permissions, that&amp;rsquo;s true but not that way in my case, maybe a cron job could do it ?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choose your password</title>
      <link>https://10degres.net/choose-your-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://10degres.net/choose-your-password/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently worked with a well known web agency in France.
They have a good reputation, they were rewarded last year for their good works and they are in the top 40 of the best french agencies. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However I was terribly surprised to find many basic errors/misconfiguration on their own site: error_reporting enable, 
SQL injection and finally a &amp;ldquo;private&amp;rdquo; admin section reachable with a simple couple of &lt;code&gt;demo&lt;/code&gt;/&lt;code&gt;demo&lt;/code&gt; as credentials&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Such vulnerability can be dangerous when using common login/password and it can be even deadly if the discovered user has high privileges.
It was true in this situation: mail contact, articles, resumes, photos everything was alterable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below the good practice to create a strong password.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-rules&#34;&gt;The rules&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;must be at least 8 characters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;must be different than your previous password&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;must NOT be related to your username&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;must NOT contain any recognizable word&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
