<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>subdomain takeover on Gwendal Le Coguic</title>
    <link>https://10degres.net/tags/subdomain-takeover/</link>
    <description>Recent content in subdomain takeover on Gwendal Le Coguic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://10degres.net/tags/subdomain-takeover/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>One takeover to rule them all</title>
      <link>https://10degres.net/one-takeover-to-rule-them-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://10degres.net/one-takeover-to-rule-them-all/</guid>
      <description>Because of Covid, the first quarantaine in France occured in March 2020. During that time I wrote a Python script to detect Subdomain Takeover. As I have been successful several times with the tool, one hit was especially beautiful.
The story of how I have been able to take control of 450+ subdomains of the national french electricity company EDF.
I&#39;m not going to explain what is subdomain takeover so take a look at the following articles if you want to know more: OWASP test guide</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain enumeration</title>
      <link>https://10degres.net/subdomain-enumeration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://10degres.net/subdomain-enumeration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A friend recently asked me what methods I use to find subdomains.
To be honest I was confused, like &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;oooohhh so much, brute force mmm&amp;hellip; zone transfer and&amp;hellip; brute for&amp;hellip; wait Google and mmm&amp;hellip; many other tools!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;
What a shame that I was so inaccurate after so much time spent to look for subdomains.
Time to dig a little bit!
After I wrote a list of the most popular methods, I tried to make a list of some tools and online resources to exploit them.
Of course this list is far from exhaustive, there are many new stuff every day, but it&amp;rsquo;s still a good start :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain takeover - DNS expiration</title>
      <link>https://10degres.net/subdomain-takeover-dns-expiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://10degres.net/subdomain-takeover-dns-expiration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One quick and easy way to make cash in bug bounty job is subdomain takeover.
The goal is to steal a forgetted/unused subdomain of your target and put a PoC in place.
If you are able to do that, that means that instead of a plain text file, an attacker could replicate the true site of the victim and perform phishing.
This way he could trick users and even the employees of the company to grab useful data like credentials, this can also have really huge impact on the companies reputation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all you have to find a list of subdomains of your target.
To perform that task, you can use a single tool like &lt;a href=&#34;https://10degres.net/theharvester/&#34;&gt;TheHarvester&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/darkoperator/dnsrecon&#34;&gt;DNSRecon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
