<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>subdomain on 10degres</title>
    <link>http://10degres.net/tags/subdomain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in subdomain on 10degres</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://10degres.net/tags/subdomain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain enumeration</title>
      <link>http://10degres.net/subdomain-enumeration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10degres.net/subdomain-enumeration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A friend recently asked me what methods I use to find subdomains.
To be honest I was confused, like &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;oooohhh so much, brute force mmm&amp;hellip; zone transfer and&amp;hellip; brute for&amp;hellip; wait Google and mmm&amp;hellip; many other tools!&amp;quot;&lt;/em&gt;
What a shame that I was so inaccurate after so much time spent to look for subdomains.
Time to dig a little bit!
After I wrote a list of the most popular methods, I tried to make a list of some tools and online resources to exploit them.
Of course this list is far from exhaustive, there are many new stuff every day, but it&amp;rsquo;s still a good start :)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bug Bounty program that changed my life</title>
      <link>http://10degres.net/the-bug-bounty-program-that-changed-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10degres.net/the-bug-bounty-program-that-changed-my-life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a real story or not, that occured in mid 2017 or not, about a private program or not, on Hackerone or not, believe me or not, but it changed my life.
I would like to thanks all the people from this company I talked with.
They were very nice with me, very fast to fix the bugs and I always got the rewards in less than 7 days, frequently the day of the report, even for the smallest bugs.
Thanks to them, I wish we could find more program like this one.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massive pwnage</title>
      <link>http://10degres.net/massive-pwnage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10degres.net/massive-pwnage/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There is different ways to hunt for vulnerabilities, depending of your knowledge, your skills, your expectation and how you like to chase.
I personally love programming and, as a true developper, I&amp;rsquo;m lazy, so I love to automate things.
By writing some piece of code or by combining multiple tools, you can find a lot of interesting stuff.
This article is about some scripts/tricks I wrote/use to perform massive tests:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;XSS with PhantomJS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heroku subdomain takeover&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Amazon S3 buckets theft&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subdomain takeover - DNS expiration</title>
      <link>http://10degres.net/subdomain-takeover-dns-expiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10degres.net/subdomain-takeover-dns-expiration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One quick and easy way to make cash in bug bounty job is subdomain takeover.
The goal is to steal a forgetted/unused subdomain of your target and put a PoC in place.
If you are able to do that, that means that instead of a plain text file, an attacker could replicate the true site of the victim and perform phishing.
This way he could trick users and even the employees of the company to grab useful data like credentials, this can also have really huge impact on the companies reputation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all you have to find a list of subdomains of your target.
To perform that task, you can use a single tool like &lt;a href=&#34;http://10degres.net/theharvester/&#34;&gt;TheHarvester&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/darkoperator/dnsrecon&#34;&gt;DNSRecon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
