<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ctf on 10degres</title>
    <link>http://10degres.net/tags/ctf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ctf on 10degres</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://10degres.net/tags/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Hunter Games</title>
      <link>http://10degres.net/the-hunter-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10degres.net/the-hunter-games/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What if bug bounty platforms had their own contest?
Imagine a tournament where bug hunters would be promoted and sponsored by platforms like in every (e-)sports.
Imagine an event where they could fight on a dedicated scope as it would be in a CTF event but with bounties or a Hackerone event but with a huge competition in the background.
This is THE HUNTER GAMES.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fail at CTF h1-212 - The Evil Job</title>
      <link>http://10degres.net/fail-at-ctf-h1-212-the-evil-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://10degres.net/fail-at-ctf-h1-212-the-evil-job/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hackerone recently released a CTF created by &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/jobertabma&#34;&gt;Jobert Abma&lt;/a&gt;. Even if I didn&amp;rsquo;t complete the challenge, it was so exciting and I was so close from the solution that I wanted to share a writeup.
Here is the tweet that tiggered the war:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hackers, hack your way to NYC this December for h1-212! An engineer of &lt;a href=&#34;http://acme.org&#34;&gt;http://acme.org&lt;/a&gt; launched a new server for a new admin panel. He is completely confident that the server can’t be hacked, so he hid a flag. Details: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hackerone.com/blog/hack-your-way-to-nyc-this-december-for-h1-212&#34;&gt;https://www.hackerone.com/blog/hack-your-way-to-nyc-this-december-for-h1-212&lt;/a&gt; …. #TogetherWeHitHarder&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here is the full description:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An engineer of acme.org launched a new server for a new admin panel at http://104.236.20.43/. He is completely confident that the server can’t be hacked. He added a tripwire that notifies him when the flag file is read. He also noticed that the default Apache page is still there, but according to him that’s intentional and doesn’t hurt anyone. Your goal? Read the flag!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
